https://www.nortonlifelock.com/about/legal

Legal Information and Resources
Find legal information and resources you need for your NortonLifeLock products and services.
Service Terms and Licenses
License and Services Agreement
See our latest service terms for device security, online privacy, and identity theft protection offerings.
LEARN MORE
LifeLock Service Terms (legacy)
Our standalone service terms for identity theft protection plans.
LEARN MORE
Norton Agreements (Legacy Software, End User, Service Agreements)
Our license and service agreements for legacy or certain standalone Norton and SurfEasy products.
LEARN MORE
LifeLock Prior ID Theft Remediation Service Terms
Our service terms for standalone identity theft remediation for events prior to membership.
LEARN MORE
Privacy Monitor Service Terms
Our service terms for the Privacy Monitor feature in our identity theft protection plans.
LEARN MORE
Insurance Coverage (United States)
Insurance Coverage for all members except NY and WA State Residents1:
United Specialty Insurance Company, Inc. Evidence of Coverage for Stolen Identity Events Occurring on or after September 1, 2019
United Specialty Insurance Company, Inc. Evidence of Coverage for Stolen Identity Events Occurring July 1, 2016 to August 31, 2019
Insurance Coverage for New York State Residents1:
State National Insurance Company, Inc. Certificate of Insurance for Stolen Identity Events Occurring on or after September 1, 2019
State National Insurance Company, Inc. Certificate of Insurance for Stolen Identity Events Occurring July 1, 2016 to August 31, 2019
Insurance Coverage for Washington State Residents1:
United Specialty Insurance Company, Inc. Evidence of Coverage for Stolen Identity Events Occurring on or after September 1, 2019
United Specialty Insurance Company, Inc. Evidence of Coverage for Stolen Identity Events Occurring July 1, 2016 to August 31, 2019
Insurance Coverage (Canada)
Insurance Coverage (except Quebec)1:
American Bankers Insurance Company of Florida, an Assurant company, Evidence of Coverage providing an aggregate limit of coverage up to $25,000 CAN or up to $100,000 CAN or up to $1 Million CAN Reimbursement Coverage.
1Please call 1-800-LifeLock for a copy of the applicable Master Policy.
Terms of Sale
Our terms related to your purchase of a subscription or membership.
LEARN MORE
Renewal Price List
Our subscription or membership renewal pricing.
LEARN MORE
Cancellation and Refund Policy
Our cancellation and refund policy related to the purchase and/or sale of a subscription or membership.
LEARN MORE
Privacy
Privacy Center
Find information on common privacy topics and how we collect and use your information through our products and services.
LEARN MORE
Global Privacy Statement
Our Privacy Statement provides an overview of how we process and protect your personal data.
LEARN MORE
Service or Product Specific Privacy Notices
Detailed information about how specific products and services collect and use your personal data.
LEARN MORE
Data Subject Access Request
Find information about exercising your privacy rights, or if you have questions about our use of your Personal Data and its privacy.
LEARN MORE
Permissions and Compliance
Copyright Policy
Learn more about our DMCA Notice and Procedure for copyrighted materials.
LEARN MORE
Export Compliance
Find information on our global export and import compliance practices.
LEARN MORE
Trademark Usage Guidelines
Assist us in protecting our brand by following our Trademark Usage Guidelines.
LEARN MORE
Social Media, Influencer Policy
Our policy for influencers blogging, posting on social media, or making statements about the NortonLifeLock brand and offerings.
LEARN MORE
More Legal Resources
Anti-Piracy
Find information about piracy, fraud, and other abuses, including how to report suspicious activities.
LEARN MORE
U.S. Law Enforcement Legal Process Guidelines
Review our policies and guidelines for law enforcement agencies seeking disclosure of information.
LEARN MORE
Code of Conduct
How we align our business practices with our values.
LEARN MORE
Website Terms of Use
By visiting and using the information and offerings available on our website, you agree to be bound by these terms.
LEARN MORE
Virtual Patent Marking
Find information about our virtual patent marking practices.
LEARN MORE
Back to Top
About NortonLifeLock
|
Careers
|
News
|
System Status
© 2019–2020 NortonLifeLock Inc. All rights reserved. NortonLifeLock, the NortonLifeLock Logo, the Checkmark Logo, Norton, LifeLock, and the LockMan Logo are trademarks or registered trademarks of NortonLifeLock Inc. or its affiliates in the United States and other countries.
Other names may be trademarks of their respective owners.
United States
© 2019–2020 NortonLifeLock Inc. All rights reserved. NortonLifeLock, the NortonLifeLock Logo, the Checkmark Logo, Norton, LifeLock, and the LockMan Logo are trademarks or registered trademarks of NortonLifeLock Inc. or its affiliates in the United States and other countries.
Other names may be trademarks of their respective owners.
